[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Shadow Punisher]
[Divine Constable Tally]
[Episode 3]
How did he get here before us?
Li Qingyang,
do you know the punishment
for breaking out of prison?
Lady Constable Frost,
this isn't the first time
I've broken out of prison.
Besides,
the shackles of your Divine Constable Bureau
can't trap me.
Instead of sitting and waiting there,
being wronged by you,
I'd rather take the initiative to move
and catch the real culprit to prove my innocence.
This way,
even if I
have offended your bureau a lot,
I can make up for it.
Right?
Chief,
if we run into Li Qingyang,
what should we do?
This person is highly suspicious.
If he's caught,
bring him back to the bureau.
I'll interrogate him in person.
If he still won't behave,
don't push too hard.
Observe his words and actions.
Only then can you know what he's up to.
Alright,
let me see
how you prove your innocence.
Please.
Thank you, Lady Constable Frost.
According to what the Advisor said,
he saw the coroner, Wen Nansheng,
carrying this bundle out.
Undoubtedly,
inside this bag are
Master Sun's body parts.
And Wen Nansheng
abandoned the body here and fled.
Tell us something we don't know.
Wen Nansheng's jade pendant?
This head is indeed Master Sun's,
but only the upper half of the body is his.
The lower half isn't.
Are you so sure, Constable Frost?
I can tell everything about a body
that I've handled at a glance.
Judging from the corpse's swollen legs,
they were mostly caused
by the coroner's long exposure to damp places.
The jade pendant left on these clothes
belongs to Wen Nansheng.
But judging from the cut,
the murder weapon is still
the silk thread used to control puppet dolls.
I got it.
The murderer first killed Master Sun
and then killed Wen Nansheng.
He mixed the lower half
of Wen Nansheng's body
with the upper half
of Master Sun's body.
Then he took away
the lower half of Master Sun.
He did this
to make people mistakenly believe
that from beginning to end,
there was only one corpse—
Master Sun's body.
Continue.
Ms. Bai,
does Dead Bone Spice have the effect of warding off evil?
It is indeed recorded in the Strange Medicines Chapter.
Why do you ask?
Last night, Mr. Meng and I were
repeatedly caught in illusions.
But today,
we are both completely fine.
You mean
the scent of Dead Bone Spice on the silk thread
broke the illusion formation?
No wonder.
A lot of young women were
murdered in Tianhuang City.
This shows the murderer
needs a large amount of Dead Bone Spice
to safely enter
the Black Wind Forest in Dougu County.
It seems that Dead Bone Spice is
going to be a key clue next.
Don't forget
about the puppet doll
that abducted the children.
Puppet doll?
It's all based on eyewitness statements.
Did you see it?
Not exactly.
Li Qingyang,
I still remember
the puppet doll found
in your Star-Gathering Pavilion.
What on earth are you up to?
My Lord, My Lady,
there's no time to waste.
Most of the spice shops here
don't sell Dead Bone Spice,
but
we should still go try our luck.
Perhaps
there will be new clues.
Ms. Bai,
what do you mean by this?
Sealed acupoints with golden needles.
Your lightness skill is marvelous.
I have to be on guard.
Sorry for that.
[Dougu]
[Tumi House]
My Lord, My Lady,
this is the most famous spice shop
in our county.
Tumi House?
Bro,
why are you carrying
a puppet doll on your back?
This?
I borrowed it from a troupe.
It's just a normal puppet
for those eyewitnesses to identify.
But they all said they didn't see it clearly.
[Tumi House]
Li Qingyang.
Who allowed you to go in?
Ms. Bai,
my acupoints are sealed with golden needles.
What tricks can I possibly play now?
My Lord, My Lady,
please be extra careful going in.
What do you mean?
Something happened to this shop not long ago.
The owner of this shop
has gone mad.
I
missed you so much.
You look unfamiliar, sir.
What brings you
to my Tumi House?
I'm here
to ask about a kind of spice.
Could it be
Dead Bone Spice?
Sir,
I am still
an unmarried maiden.
Staring at me like this is
quite impertinent.
It really is Dead Bone Spice.
How could this be?
Why are you surprised?
Refining Dead Bone Spice
requires the blood of young girls
with pure Yin birth characters.
In the past, if a poor girl
who met the conditions fell terminally ill,
she would be sold to spice refiners,
who used her body to refine the Spice.
This was a way to earn money for her family
in her final days.
Exactly.
The rare Dead Bone Spice
in Tianhuang City's black market
mostly comes from this.
Such an opportunity is
hard to come by even in decades.
So even across the entire Great Shi,
the supply of Dead Bone Spice is very limited.
I didn't expect
that such a remote, rural backwater like Dougu County
would have this rare Dead Bone Spice.
Tumi House was burglarized
2 months ago.
Actually, not too many spices were
missing from the House.
But
somehow,
the owner of this shop
seemed to have
suffered a great hit
and gone mad.
Two months ago?
The case of refining the Spice with young girls in Tianhuang City
and the disappearance of children in Dougu County
were both...
They both started 2 months ago.
Could the stolen item be Dead Bone Spice?
I have never seen that legendary
and precious item,
so I'm not too sure either.
Who robbed the spice shop?
Has the case been solved?
Well...
You can neither find the missing children
nor catch a petty thief!
Your Dougu County government is really...
My Lady,
you can't blame it on us.
This theft case is really
quite bizarre.
As you can see,
to keep the fragrance,
Tumi House has sealed all the windows here.
The only opening is this door.
The spices here are so precious
that the owner would lock the door
when he closes the shop every day.
After the incident,
we also checked the lock,
and it was intact.
In a situation like this,
unless...
Unless it was a ghost manifesting,
how else could
this be explained?
No other entrance or exit besides the door?
Then what is this?
Ms. Bai,
this dog hole is too small
even for a 7-year-old child
to get in,
let alone a thief.
You may go out first.
Bring Young Master Qingyang out, too.
Understood.
Don't bother.
I will leave by myself.
He is right.
Even one who masters
the Bone-Shrinking Technique or something
can't get out.
Unless
the thief is the size of a child.
The puppet doll...
What is this?
Puppetry.
I've learned it.
Lady Constable Frost,
didn't you find one
in my Star-Gathering Pavilion?
What?
Have you forgotten?
I didn't expect you to still be able to perform
puppetry with your acupoints sealed by golden needles.
I really underestimated you.
Sealing acupoints with golden needles restricts inner power.
What does it have to do with controlling a puppet?
Are
inner power masters the only ones in the world
who can perform puppetry?
At least it proves
that a puppet doll can crawl through this dog hole
to steal the Dead Bone Spice.
So the spice thief is
someone who can
control puppet dolls.
I don't think so.
Firstly,
many people can control puppets.
Secondly,
actually, a puppet doll
can't steal the Dead Bone Spice.
I did this experiment
just to prove this point.
Indeed,
it can crawl in.
However,
what happens after it crawls in?
A puppet is not a dog.
How could it steal the Spice?
You are just a beginner in puppetry.
Just because you can't do it
doesn't mean your accomplice can't.
Lady Constable Frost,
puppetry is basically
an extension of the hands.
A puppet is not a human.
It cannot see or think.
If the murderer outside the dog hole
couldn't see the situation inside,
it'd be absolutely impossible for him
to control the puppet
to steal the Dead Bone Spice from inside.
Unless
someone can train a puppet
to have a mind.
Otherwise,
as long as it's just puppetry,
it's definitely impossible to achieve this.
Seems like
the clue has gone cold again.
My Lord, My Lady,
do you want to hear
the clues I've found?
The spices brought in by this Tumi House
in Dougu County are famous far and wide.
It's said
that the original owner here was
a graceful young woman.
Everyone called her Lady Fragrance.
But now, look
at this shop owner in front of us.
If you call him a lady,
everyone in Dougu County
must be blind.
Then who exactly is this person?
Two months ago,
the Dead Bone Spice in Tianhuang City's black market was
so valuable and hard to come by.
You two also know about this.
Soon after,
Lady Fragrance disappeared without a trace.
At this time,
here in Tumi House,
a heavily made-up Mr. Fragrance
appeared out of nowhere.
I heard
that Lady Fragrance
has an elder brother.
You mean
the brother killed his younger sister
to refine Dead Bone Spice and rake in profits?
This blood-stained,
invaluable Dead Bone Spice
was stolen overnight.
Since then, he has turned
into the way he is now.
The county government couldn't find evidence
to prove he committed murder,
and neither did they find
Lady Fragrance's body.
Given his current state,
County Magistrate Du
just left him alone.
Brother,
you're here.
I
missed you so much.
If the spice thief is
the murderer we're looking for,
then everything lines up.
Exactly.
A puppet doll was used in the case of refining the Spice
with young girls in Tianhuang City.
The missing children here were
also abducted by puppet dolls.
If the murderer stole the Dead Bone Spice
in order to break
the illusion formation in the Black Wind Forest,
then why on earth
did he want to enter the Black Wind Forest?
What a pity.
Young Master Qingyang demonstrated it himself,
said it with certainty,
and proved that puppetry
couldn't help steal the Spice from a locked room.
So...
Investigating to this point,
the clue has gone cold again.
My Lord, My Lady,
have you ever thought about
why those children's graves
in the Black Wind Forest are empty?
Let's assume those children are not dead.
If they're not dead,
why are there tombstones erected for them?
Those children will die sooner or later.
Two months ago,
the murderer abducted the children
not for ransom. The motive is a mystery.
You should go back
and start by investigating the children.
Here.
[Map of Dougu County]
And here.
These alley entrances are
on the only route from the county
to the Black Wind Forest.
You must strictly guard them
day and night.
Once suspicious people are spotted,
arrest them immediately.
Understood!
Let's go.
How is it?
I've checked the household records several times.
Some children's families are farmers,
some sell vegetables,
and some do small businesses.
There are boys and girls, older and younger.
Except for being children,
they have nothing in common.
Is everything ready?
It's time to set off.
Where are we going?
Li Si,
you trespassed into the government morgue,
broke out of prison, impersonated an official,
and interfered with the investigation.
You are now being arrested and escorted back to Tianhuang City
to stand trial.
Go.
Got it.
Mr. Meng,
will Lady Constable Frost
run into danger
staying here alone?
What if that culprit
has some tricks up his sleeve?
Every extra day those children
stay here just makes things
more dangerous for them.
Who on earth are you?
Why do you care so much about this case?
Or rather,
do those missing children
have anything to do with you?
Go.
My Lord!
My Lord, My Lord!
Is there any news of my son, Yuanbao?
No. Not yet.
Stop running.
Come over here.
We'll butcher the pig later
and offer its head to the Earth God,
begging the Earth God
to bless my son Yuanbao to come home as soon as possible.
Yuyao, be careful.
Erbao, stop digging.
There's no food there,
only Yuanbao's tooth.
Tooth?
Come here, little piggy.
Time to eat grass.
Madam!
What is it digging for over there?
Yuanbao's tooth.
According
to our local custom,
upper teeth go to the ground; lower teeth go to the sky.
I took our Yuanbao's
fallen incisor
and buried it there.
Incisor?
Mr. Meng.
Aren't you looking for
what those children have in common?
I think I've figured it out.
Mr. Wang, look.
Yuanbao has
reached the stage of losing teeth
and often complains of toothaches.
My teeth hurt so much.
I see.
Mother,
it's my sister's tooth.
My Lord! My Lady!
In the other homes
of the missing children,
we also found their shed baby teeth.
The murderer is indeed
looking for kids
who are losing their baby teeth.
Now we have a direction.
Ask them to make a list
of children who are losing their baby teeth
and set up ambushes to catch the culprit.
Li Qingyang!
He got away again.
Forget it.
We'll catch him eventually.
The priority is to find the kids losing their teeth.
[Dougu County Office]
My Lord!
[Enter the County Office to Examine Oneself]
[Righteous Dougu County Magistrate]
My Lord, this...
My Lord.
My Lord, My Lady,
we've got the complete list.
It's the full list
of all the kids who are losing
their baby teeth in Dougu County.
[Chunfeng Hall, Sun Yuyao]
Yuyao?
Why is there only one kid?
My Lady,
Dougu County is
a very small place.
And with years of droughts,
crop failures, and a population decline,
there can't be many children left!
The night the children went missing,
why did the murderer take all the children
except for Yuyao?
That night, Yuyao was with me
at the county office.
The murderer didn't have a chance.
But now Mrs. Hua is taking care of her.
Let's go.
My Lord! My Lady! Bad news!
[Righteous Dougu County Magistrate]
My Lady!
What's up?
Bad news!
Yuyao is missing!
My Lord, My Lady.
Weren't there staff from the county office watching her?
I just went to put the freshly butchered pig's head
in the Earth God Temple.
When I turned around,
Yuyao was just gone.
My Lord, My Lady, what should we do?
Let's find Yuyao first.
[Enter the County Office to Examine Oneself]
Tanghulu (candied haws)!
Eat slowly.
[Rice Shop]
Tanghulu (candied haws)!
-I want one, too! -Kiddo, want some tanghulu?
Here you are.
Come and see!
Let's go, Yuyao.
Take care!
Let's go look over there.
Little girl.
-A little hat! -You've got good taste. This one's pretty.
Sir, take a look.
Come on.
The tiger one looks energetic.
Yuyao.
Madam.
I want to see the one behind.
So pretty.
Yuyao,
have you had fun today?
Yes.
If only Yuanbao, Erniu, and Cuicui were
here, too.
Mr. Young Master,
were they really
taken away by bad guys?
Yuyao,
I promise you
I will definitely save your friends
from the bad guys.
Okay?
Don't forget to beat up the bad guys, too.
Of course I will beat up the bad guys.
I hate those
who bully children the most.
Let's go.
Boss.
You haven't paid!
That bottle
is worth
your entire stall.
It smells so good!
It's Dead Bone Spice.
Where did you get this bottle?
A gentleman used it
to pay just now.
The symbol of the Star-Gathering Pavilion.
[Gathering]
Li Qingyang.
Did you see that gentleman
have a child by his side?
Yes!
He was with a little girl.
He took Yuyao away.
If he were the murderer,
he wouldn't have helped us investigate the cases all along.
What I'm worried about now is
that even if he's on our side
and wants to help us catch the murderer,
Yuyao could still be in danger.
Meng, think about it.
Why did he take Yuyao away?
Simply because he knew Yuyao was
the last child.
If he uses Yuyao as bait,
the murderer will definitely show up.
This bastard!
How dare he treat a child's life
like it's nothing!
[Chunfeng Hall]
Emperor of Heaven,
Emperor of Earth,
there's a boy in my home crying at night.
-Gentlemen passing by, -Here he comes, as expected.
read it three times,
and he will sleep soundly until daybreak.
Yuyao,
Yuyao!
Come out and play.
[Chunfeng Hall]
Come on.
Come out.
Let's play together.
Let's have fun together.
My Lord, My Lady.
You came neither early nor late,
just in time.
Mr. Meng,
it's too late.
Yuyao's mind has already been seized
by the puppet doll.
If we act rashly,
Yuyao might be in graver danger.
Good point, Ms. Bai.
Now,
we just need to wait for the puppet doll
to take Yuyao to its destination.
The murderer will let his or her guard down by then.
That way,
we'll have a better chance.
I didn't expect
you to actually use Yuyao as bait!
Who was it that kept saying
hurting children is unforgivable?
Mr. Meng,
if you are done lecturing me,
why don't we go after them together?
How's that?
[Chunfeng Hall]
Golden needles blocked my channels,
and a heavy strike sealed my acupoints.
Great,
even an immortal can't escape now.
Li Si,
I hate people who disregard
children's lives the most in my life.
Once the murderer is brought to justice,
I swear I'll throw you
into the Divine Constable Bureau's prison!
Let's go.
Dead Bone Spice?
As expected,
the missing children from the county are
right in this Black Wind Forest.
So this Dead Bone Spice
can not only break
the illusion formation in the Black Wind Forest
but also open a path through these flowers.
This proves
we've found the right way.
There seems to be some writing
behind this spider web.
This is
the writing of Liluo?
I recognize it,
but I don't know what it means.
The Kingdom of Liluo that was
destroyed by the late Emperor Wuzong of Shi
47 years ago?
Could it be
that the puppet dolls
and the incident from 17 years ago
have something to do with the Kingdom of Liluo?
Zhenzhu?
Meng Rui!
Li Si!
What...
Let me check.
It's nothing.
I'm fine.
It's just that I was stabbed
by Lord Constable Ghost last time.
Now the wound has reopened.
It won't kill me.
Sorry.
Li Si,
thank you for saving us.
My Lord, My Lady, what's this for?
I'm fine.
The priority is to save them.
Let's go.
It was originally a sure thing.
I didn't expect that Li Si
would risk his own life
to break through the sealed acupoints
and save those two from the Divine Constable Bureau.
You've really disappointed me.
Please rest assured!
I will protect God Kelu
and the Sacred Moluo Fruit
even at the cost of my life!
So big.
This flower must be
the mother plant
of those bizarre flowers outside.
Inside these are all children!
It's Yuanbao.
Yuanbao.
Yuanbao!
The person who set up Spider's Tear
must be nearby.
Be careful.
Show yourself!
May I
have your name, lady?
How dare you profane the Sacred Moluo Fruit?
It's livor mortis.
Wait a minute.
Don't you think
the dress of the woman in front of us
looks very familiar?
Tumi House was burglarized
2 months ago.
But
somehow,
the owner of this shop
seemed to have
suffered a great hit
and gone mad.
Lady Fragrance?
The person in front of us
must be the long-missing
real owner of Tumi House,
Lady Fragrance.
You guessed it right.
Her elder brother used her blood
to refine Dead Bone Spice.
And I used her body
to make a human puppet.
Compared to puppet dolls,
this lifelike human puppet is
far superior.
Come out!
Or I'll cut down this flower!
The only chance of survival for these children
relies entirely
on the great Tianmoluo.
If the flower dies,
they won't survive either!
This Spirit of Tianmoluo is
a remnant from the ancient Liluo Sect.
These Moluo Flowers in the canyon are
all its descendants.
It is the soul of God Kelu!
Liluo fell
47 years ago.
You were the one who transplanted it here?
Forty-seven years ago,
the Shi Empire wiped out Liluo,
committing atrocious crimes!
Tianmoluo taking root here was
the will of God Kelu.
It's going to use the lifeblood of the Great Shi's children
to grow the fruits of revenge!